let me tell you something about police
work for a change let me tell you
something real quick in my in having it
a speeding ticket yeah really you know
why you got it
because you deserve it right you guys
don't listen the speed limit says define
that's what it says that's the limit Oh
officer don't they allow you five miles
no where does the sign say 55 but if
you're famous oh come on the radio go on
take five all for yourself
8:55 with a little winky emoji on a 6'5
you go to the mountains you get on the
edge of the mountain the signs say this
is your limit you don't go hey let's
take five more steps and if you get a
ticket just tell you the ticket pay the
ticket don't try to bribe the officer
I've had guys offered me cash I had a
guy off of me cocaine oh yeah that's
real smart don't pay $150 ticket go to
jail for two years how about that's a
good trade-off I had a person once say
to me I'll show you my breasts if you
let me off the ticket I'll say good
listen no no sir you don't have to do
that
you can leave but no
yeah sometimes let me tell you guys
something about police on the inside
police work sometimes you'll see two
officers working together they don't
always get along you know I've had some
bad partners I just one partner I hated
that guy who do is yell at me don't
touch the log sheet don't touch the
radio
understand what I'm saying yeah don't
touch anything I understand yeah yeah
then you go back and tell the captain
Jordan just said say you won't touch the
long she won't touch anything officer
Tucker was his date talk about well
Tucker we'll leave it there so one day
me and Tucker get a call and we make an
arrest
I'm putting the guy away in the holding
cell no you put a got away in a holding
cell you take off all your weapons take
off your primary weapon
take off your secondary weapon pick up
your mace take off everything you lock
it away that way there's no accidents
when you put them away so I'm processing
the guy there's a bang on the glass it's
Tucker come on we got to go we got to go
there's a 211 and Winchell's right up
the street come on now for those of you
who don't know
Winchell's it's a donut shop in Los
Angeles if you're a criminal robbing a
donut shop two blocks from a police
station it's pretty certain we're gonna
catch you so he's banging on the glass
come on we gotta go we gotta go
so I'm like I haven't finished press
come on come on we gotta go so out we
goes run jump in the cruiser we get over
there halfway there I realize I have no
weapons on me we get to Winchell's just
as the two guys - coming out of wind
chills we pull up
Tucker jumps out on the driver's side
pulls his weapon throws him out I jump
out on the passenger side I don't have
anything so I just point my finger
Tucker says hey I'm gonna go inside to
see if there's any more you sit out here
and you hold these guys here he runs
into the wind chills I'm saying even
they're looking at me like what's going
on
Tucker comes out looks at me I look at
him he looks at me he goes you should
take the safety off
true story I did a lot of cool things on
the job coolest thing ever did was
deliver a baby that's the coolest thing
ever done you know this woman her water
broke and it was cool because I got my
name in the LA Times the next day and
everything but this woman her water
broke and she calls her husband to come
get her and he don't show up so she
tried to drive herself to the hospital
and she panicked and pulled into a
7-eleven so much so my crews are at a
red light they ran out street got me had
to turn around and come back in and
deliver a baby and a 7-eleven got my
name in LA Times next day everything let
me tell you something
you work for LAPD they just assume you
know how a baby's born
they don't show you a video you know
puppet show nothing I never see no baby
born before I've got a baby with pop out
and maybe gonna break it pop out winner
there's a lot of things that come out of
there with that day
I thought she was having twins that's
like you know mmm one of them look like
you and the little one you're gonna have
to love him special he ugly
here's the best part you'll appreciate
this - most of it his the best part so
then when they when the EMT came and
took her to the hospital
when she pulled into 7-eleven she pulled
into a handicapped slack so wrote a card
at it towed away
[Music]
[Applause]